who hacked seven out of 16 publicly
launched companies of the Y combinator
spring batch in 30 minutes.
>> Out of these 16 companies, everybody was
using AI to build their software, but
they were in different life cycles of
stage. But then they added a new feature
through just by coding and that
ultimately caused a new vulnerability
into your system. The reality is the
best way to be able to uh security test
new software in the future as the volume
of software is changing is to look at it
from an offensive security standpoint.
The the situation right now is I think
just the very beginning of what we of
like the implications we see. Um imagine
once larger companies start adopting AI
even even at an even larger scale right
um without without thinking about
security quite as much then I think
we'll start to see some really really
bad large security breaches and in that
moment I think the entire industry will
revisit about how we implement security
in this age of you know tens of
thousands of lines of PRs every day um
because of this amazing technology that
we have uh what the security
implications of all of this, right?
>> And I then started researching and
there's some uh there's like this
statistic about like how LMS have been
generating code over the last uh last
few years and it went somewhere from
like 17% correct syntactically correct
to like 98% correct last time I checked
which is effectively almost 100%. Um,
and I was like, "Oh, that's cool." Like,
it is getting better at code. That's
awesome. But then if you look at the uh
security benchmarks, it's like flat and
like just very suddenly going down even
slightly. And I'm just like wondering,
oh wow. So now we live in a world where
we're writing exponentially more code
while the security posture of them have
not improved. And that basically creates
this Swiss cheese of a bunch of holes
all over our products uh all over the
surface area of the product. and who's
going to go fix that? Who's going to go
find all those issues? It's so much
code, right? And so that compelled me to
to start Casco, right? To really think
about how can we take a new refresh
approach on software security and try to
figure out what are the true
vulnerabilities that matter to you where
you have millions of lines of code
shipping and what are the ones that
truly are exploitable and what are the
ones to focus on, right? Um, yeah, that
that's that's a little bit of the the
background there.
>> Yeah. I'm curious, did it did it check
in your credentials to to a git repo
somewhere?
>> No, it did not. Actually, what it did is
it uh copied it and then uh prepended it
into the deployment command with CDK.
So, they had the So, so even worse, it
was actually my bash history now. So,
those those credentials are [laughter]
>> it's one of those moments where you
don't know. you almost can't be angry
because it's so impressive that it
actually found a path or a route to it,
right? And that's that's an interesting
thing like from a security point of view
there there are so many different ways
an LLM can kind of can kind of you know
come to a come to an answer or or or
find a resolution to a particular a
particular issue. It seems it's almost
like the waft style of you know that
there's if there's if you imagine an
infinite possibilities of solutions how
can you how can you even start thinking
about uh providing guidance or providing
some level of this is right you can do
this this is wrong because I guess those
those rules will change based on any
number of different factors. Um I guess
why don't we talk why don't we start
talking a little bit about um when is
the best time to to to think about
security from an LLM's point of view. Uh
if we think about code there are many
places where we can almost like
statically test where where we can ask
the LLM to to to think about things or
review code from a from a security point
of view. Uh, obviously the offensive
testing is a little bit further further
right although I say further right the
way LM are building and being able to
produce it's not that far right it's
only it's only a tiny bit more waiting
but you know should we be should we be
looking at security all the way through
or is there a best place to stop and
then say right now we should test and
this is the best way of testing what are
your thoughts on that
>> yeah I I think the software development
role is going through this massive
compression of skills, right? Like a a
parallel I would draw is maybe uh two
years ago asking a software engineer to
just build a UI without a designer
providing a Figma file or some wireframe
would be like hey it will look so bad it
would be embarrassing to ship it in
front of the clients but that's that's
changed right so I think because people
tend to be better reviewers than there
are creators that's like just the
general human being like you can always
look at something like yeah this this
looks kind of good or or bad like you
can judge it right um but creating it
exactly as somebody has painted it is
very hard right so so I think we've
already seen that happen in different
roles like obviously design certainly in
product we see great engineers who have
like um product acumen now be able to do
more because they have the time to do it
and I think we'll see that with security
as well over time now there's some
difficulties in security which is like
obviously there's statically uh these
static analysis tools that everybody I
should just have as like a baseline most
you know most integrations with GitHub
kind of um there there's many different
integrations with GitHub that kind of
brings this out of the box right so
should be a very easy switch to flip if
that makes sense um but with security it
is not just purely a software
engineering problem or just purely a
security engineering problem uh security
cannot be looked in isolation it has to
be looked at in the context of the
business, right? So, for example, if you
use a uh a a a random scanner, if you
will, right, for for like your uh for
your URLs that you expose on your
application,
it will flag that, hey, this particular
photo URL is public. You must have had
made a mistake. But what if it's Google
photos and I made that photo public by
intention? That is the business decision
I have made. And so the lack of
semantics in security technologies today
is causing all of these false positives,
noisy alarms and people are just swamped
with a bunch of different alerts and
getting paged without being actually
without without the tool actually being
aware of like, oh yeah, this actually
doesn't quite matter. It's really not
that important because this is what the
system was designed to do, right? Um,
and so I think we'll see this
compression of security into software
engineering happen, but we'll be a
little bit slower because there's even
more things that we need to kind of tie
together the business context, right?
Um, the obviously understanding security
paradigms, but also software engineering
paradigms.
And yeah, the the the thing I would
recommend for people developing uh with
specifications is also just have a
little like access control.md
file as part of your your stack
somewhere where you can just say hey
this is what I expect my end users to
do. Here are the different roles that
exist. This is what these roles are
supposed to do. After you're done
implementing, verify against these
different rules and see if they were
impacted or not and flag them back to me
or, you know, reimplement the change
with those things in mind. Something
very [clears throat] simple as that
immediately adds so much semantic
context into the code that gets
generated. So the LLM can help you be
better.